Sakti Tua Petrus Davici Banjarnahor



saktitua14@gmail.com



in https://www.linkedin.com/in/sakti-tua-petrus-davici-banjarnahor-8b8192186



081380223328

Summary

Hallo.. Introduce my self. My mame is sakti tua petrus davici banjarnahor. I am work as web developer programming. And I open for new engine or new programming language. With 4 years of professional web fullstack programming. And I am a bachelor of engginering informatics.

Experience

- Wordpress Developer (May 2018 August 2018) PT Juanto Mandiri Pratama
 - Development E-commerce view use plugin of wordpress
- Web Developer (Oct 2018 August 2020) PT Unzyp Solusi Teknologi
 - Development Client System Waskita Ready Mix online with base web
 - Development Client Microsoft Dealreg with base web.
 - Development Client Arkeolog inventory system with base web.
- Web Developer & Head Project (Sept 2020 Now) PT Teknologi Api Duasisi
 - Development Client DCG Cafee create POS System
 - Development Client Duasisi Company Profile
 - Development Payroll System with PT Duasisi Company.
 - Development Domain System Listing for save domain, username and password
 - Monitoring team in work and update progress from team.
- Web Developer Freelance Project Indonesia.tv
 - Development admin panel video streaming Indonesia.tv
- Backend Developer Indo Artha Teknologi (nov-2022 current)
 - Development system from client in fintech

Education

- Universitas Mercu buana Yogyakarta (2013 -2017) Bachelor Engginering Informatics
- SMA NEGERI 2 Binjai (2008 -2011)
- SMP ST. Thomas 2 Binjai (2008 -2011)
- SMP ST. Thomas 2 Binjai (2005 -2008)
- SD Negeri 020268 Binjai (1999 -2005)

Skill

- React js
- Framework Laravel, CI, Symfony
- Jquery, Css, html, Boostrap,
- Database , Pgsql, mysql,